let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "In which year was KFC founded",
        answer: "1952",
        options: [
            "1987",
            "1952",
            "2003",
            "1998"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which one is not a vegetable?",
        answer: "tomatoes",
        options: [
            "tomatoes",
            "carot",
            "patatoes",
            "kale"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which type of beans are used to make baked beans?",
        answer: " Haricot beans",
        options: [
            "Cannellini beans",
            "Flageolet beans",
            "Borlotti beans",
            " Haricot beans"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Bobotie is the national dish of which country?",
        answer: "South Africa",
        options: [
            "Nigeria",
            "Ethiopia",
            "South Africa",
            "Kenya"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: " Which of the following does not feature on the ingredients list of Worcestershire Sauce?",
        answer: " Tomatoes",
        options: [
            "Tamarind",
            "Anchovies",
            "Anchovies",
            "Tomatoes"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: " Gruyère is a cheese from which country?",
        answer: "Switzerland",
        options: [
            "Switzerland",
            "Austria",
            "France",
            "France"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: " What is the tang on a knife?",
        answer: " The part of the knife blade that extends down into the handle",
        options: [
            "The leather case to secure the knife",
            "The tip of the blade",
            "The length of the sharp edge",
            " The part of the knife blade that extends down into the handle"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Roughly how much does a medium egg (still in its shell) weigh in the UK?",
        answer: "53-63g",
        options: [
            "23-33g",
            "33-43g",
            "53-63g",
            "63-73g"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which of these best describes the Austrian dish Kaiserschmarrn?",
        answer: "Fluffy, raisin pancakes that are chopped or broken into small chunks and dusted with icing sugar",
        options: [
            "Thin crêpes that are rolled, filled with jam and dusted with icing sugar",
            "Fluffy, raisin pancakes that are chopped or broken into small chunks and dusted with icing sugar",
            "Layers of crêpes and cream, stacked to form a pancake cake",
            "A stock, served with thin strips of leftover pancakes"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What is a hop?",
        answer: "A climbing plant, the flowers of which are used in beer",
        options: [
            "A climbing plant, the roots of which are used in beer",
            "A climbing plant, the flowers of which are used in beer",
            "A climbing plant, the leaves of which are used in beer",
            " A grain crop used in beer"
        ]
    }
];